[{"answer": "Welcome to Northeastern Bank.  Can I help you", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Hi.  Im here because I wanted to open up a new account", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Welcome to Northeastern Bank.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " OK.  Do you see the gentleman sitting at the desk over there", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Hi.  Im here because I wanted to open up a new account", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": " OK.  Do you see the gentleman sitting at the desk over there", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Thats Mr. Gordon, our accounts specialist.  Please see him and he can assis", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Thats Mr. Gordon, our accounts specialist.  Please see him and he can assis", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Hello, there.  What can I do for you", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Id like to open up a checking account", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Hello, there.  What can I do for you", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "I can help you with that.  Do you currently have an account with us", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Id like to open up a checking account", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " No", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 24, "question": "I can help you with that.  Do you currently have an account with us", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Great.  Thank you for choosing Northeastern as your bank today.  Now", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 28, "question": " No", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": "An individual account", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Great.  Thank you for choosing Northeastern as your bank today.  Now", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Are you a student", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 33, "question": "An individual account", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " No, I work for Coca Cola here in Boston", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Are you a student", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Thats not a Boston accent.  Where are you from", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 35, "question": " No, I work for Coca Cola here in Boston", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " From Alaska.  I just moved here to Boston last week", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Thats not a Boston accent.  Where are you from", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Great.  Welcome to Boston.  I think our basic checking account might b", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 37, "question": " From Alaska.  I just moved here to Boston last week", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I think that sounds good.  The minimum balance wont be a problem for me", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Great.  Welcome to Boston.  I think our basic checking account might b", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Very good.  So, to open the account I will need to see your ID and wel", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I think that sounds good.  The minimum balance wont be a problem for me", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Very good.  So, to open the account I will need to see your ID and wel", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " How much will you be depositing today", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 50, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Id like to put this check for $5000 into the account.  I already signed the back o", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 51, "question": " How much will you be depositing today", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Alright.  Wait here just one moment while I take this over to the teller t", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Id like to put this check for $5000 into the account.  I already signed the back o", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Alright.  Wait here just one moment while I take this over to the teller t", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " OK, the deposit is made, and weve opened up your account.  Do yo", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 60, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yes.  What about my checks and ATM card", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 64, "question": " OK, the deposit is made, and weve opened up your account.  Do yo", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Today well give you a few temporary checks and your debit card shoul", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Yes.  What about my checks and ATM card", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I think the standard will be fine", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Today well give you a few temporary checks and your debit card shoul", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " What color would you like, blue, green, or gold", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I think the standard will be fine", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Gold, please", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 75, "question": " What color would you like, blue, green, or gold", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " OK.  You should receive those in 12 to 14 days.  Let me mention also tha", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Gold, please", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Oh, is this free", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " OK.  You should receive those in 12 to 14 days.  Let me mention also tha", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Its a free service along with your account, but there is a $50 service fe", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Oh, is this free", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " I see.  Id better not overdraw my account then", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Its a free service along with your account, but there is a $50 service fe", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yes, its just set up in case you do.  Now, would you also like to open ", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 87, "question": " I see.  Id better not overdraw my account then", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " No, I dont think so.  Not right now", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Yes, its just set up in case you do.  Now, would you also like to open ", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " No problem.  Is there anything else I can do for you today or any othe", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 92, "question": " No, I dont think so.  Not right now", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " No, I dont think so", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 96, "question": " No problem.  Is there anything else I can do for you today or any othe", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Well, It was a pleasure assisting you today Ms. Tibault.  Again, we than", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 97, "question": " No, I dont think so", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Thank you for your help.  Good-bye", "docId": "11-02", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Well, It was a pleasure assisting you today Ms. Tibault.  Again, we than", "qSentId": 100}]
